pakzindabad.com 2013-06-21

# Privacy Policy - PakZindabad

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy is derived to demonstrate our sole commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information and data. **_PakZindabad.Com_**   will not sell, distribute, barter or transfer any of your personal identifiable information to companies, organizations or other parties without your permission. Our privacy policy is designed to help you understand why we gather the minimal personal information and how we collect it. The policy also reflects our commitment to take all commercially possible and reasonable steps to ensure the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information.  
We reserve the right to make changes or alter our privacy policies and such changes or alterations will be posted on our website in timely manner.

### _**Website Traffic Analysis Software:**_

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We also monitor our traffic to analyze visitors’s information, such as, but not limited to, operating system, browsers, screen resolutions and similar.

In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

### **_How you receive Communication:_**

If you received any mailing from our side, it means your email address is listed as being an account holder or you have any relationship with our account holder and have expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”). Most of our communication will be via email. This could be in the form of announcements or services or our newsletter.

### **_Unsubscribe Options:_**

Each email sent has an easy way to unsubscribe from receiving email from the lists your have subscribed to, or to add or modify your mentioned interests. If you wish to unsubscribe, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email.

#### **_COOKIES:_**

  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
  * We use third party services to manage analytics of our website. These analytics correspond to the behavior of the visitors on our site. These analytics are collected simply with the aim and objective to further enhance and improve the visitor experience on our site

### **_Usage of Account Information:_**

Your private information is safe with _**PakZindabad.Com**_ as we will never sell your personal account information or subscriber data with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information you submit to us is only accessible to employees managing the information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services concerned to our communications with you.
